ripsink.com 2014-08-18

# Untitled Page

_WELCOME TO_ ** _RIPSINK.COM™_** _  
_  
  
To contact the RIPSINK.COM team please send an email to info@ripsink.com  
All concerns, questions, comments or suggestions are welcome. ** _RIPSINK.COM   Privacy Policy_**

By using this site, you agree to the Privacy Policy of RIPSINK.COM. If you do not agree to the Policy do not use this site. RIPSINK.COM reviews its privacy policy periodically and reserves the right, at its discretion, to modify or remove portions of this policy at any time. This page should be reviewed periodically so that you are updated on any changes. If you want to communicate with us about our policy, please e-mail us at  info@ripsink.com

 _  
_This Site contains links to other web sites that we do not own ("Third Party Sites"). Links to Third Party Sites are provided solely as a convenience to you and do not constitute any endorsement or sponsorship by RIPSINK.COM, any information, content, products, services, advertising or other materials provided or made available on or through such sites, or the owners, operators or sponsors of such sites. You acknowledge and agree that RIPSINK.COM is not responsible or liable, directly or indirectly, in connection with your use of any Third Party Sites or for any information, content, products, services, advertising or others materials provided or made available on or through such sites.

RIPSINK.COM, located at http://www.ripsink.com recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about visitors to our sites. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as your name, address or email address, is automatically collected from visitors to our sites. Personally identifiable information about visitors to our sites is collected only when knowingly and voluntarily submitted. We may collect certain non-personal information to optimize our Web pages for your computer (i.e., the identity of your Internet browser, the type of operating system you use, your IP address and the domain name of your Internet service provider). We may use such non-personal information for internal purposes, including but not limited to improving the content of our sites.  
In those instances when we do collect personally identifiable information, the following policies apply:

Notice  
RIPPSINK.COM will notify you if and when we are collecting personally identifiable information about you and how we intend to use it. For example, we may need to collect such information to provide you with information you requested, in connection with emails sent to us, or in connection with community postings or comments made by you.

Personal information may be disclosed in special situations where RIPSINK.COM has reason to believe that doing so is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone damaging, injuring, or interfering with RIPSINK.COM's rights, property, users, or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities.RIPSINK.COM may reveal information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

Cookies  
Cookies are data that a Web site transfers to an individual's hard-drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies, which are an industry standard used by most Web sites, including those operated by RIPSINK.COM, can facilitate a user's ongoing access to and use of a site. They allow us to track usage patterns and to compile data that can help us improve our content and target advertising. Our Cookies are no programs that can cause damage to a user's systems or files. If you do not want information collected through the use of Cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to deny or accept the Cookie feature. But you should note that Cookies may be necessary to provide you with features such as adding your personal favourites.Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on RIPSINK.COM.com. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Links to Third Party Sites  
RIPSINK.COM has established many links directly to sites operated by third parties. These sites are not operated or maintained by RIPSINK.COM. These sites may collect personal information from you. You should check the applicable privacy policy's of the third party site's in case you enter these sites.

RIPSINK.COM contains links to third-party sites.  RIPSINK.COM provides these links as a convenience and does not endorse the companies or content of any such sites. RIPSINK.COM does not control and not responsible for and makes no representation and warranty and disclaims all liability with respect to any such site, any content on any such site or such site's privacy practices.

For more information or to contact RIPSINK.COM please send an email addressed to our: 

Technical Support Team   [info@ripsink.com](mailto:info@ufreetv.com)

Peter Rip, Administrator 

Thank You for Visting **_RIPSINK.COM™_**
